Listen, you know what, sir?
For the last time
I don't care
what the computer says.
We did not take
a bag of Meshuga nuts
from the mini-bar
and we did not watch
Doctor Do Me a Little.
Hey.
Oh, Joey, were you in our room
last night?
No.
I was told the name of the movie
would not appear on the bill.
Hi.
We're checking out
of the bridal suite.
That's right.
I'm no longer
a bride.
I'll never be
a bride again.
Now I'm just
someone's wife.
And I'm the happiest guy
in the world.
Oh, come on, honey.
Don't be upset.
We still have so much
to look forward to.
Oh, yeah, right.
We've got the honeymoon.
Oh, that's not
till Thursday.
The wedding pictures.
Those won't be
ready for weeks.
Not the disposable cameras
from the tables.
That's true.
I knew I married
you for a reason.
I'll tell you what.
I will got get them developed,
and you can go home.
Okay.
( chuckling )
What? What did you take
a picture of?
Nothing.
It was something, huh?
Okay, Ross has the cameras.
Has he checked out yet?
Are you joking?
No.
Checkout is
not till noon
and he has a good
11 minutes left.
So?
So, Ross has never
checked out of a room
a minute before he had to.
Yeah. One time
when we were dating
we got a late checkout.
He got so excited,
it was the best
sex we ever had.
Until, you know
he screamed out
"Radisson" at the end.
Okay, well,
I'm going to get Ross
get the cameras,
and get them developed.
( chuckles )
32, Joe.
You're 32.
Here's a copy of your bill.
Oh, thanks.
Champagne, strawberries.
Oh, my God!
I can't believe
Chandler ordered porn
on our wedding night.
Yeah, that's sad.
Meshuga nut?
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's DOA ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
( knocking at door )
Hi.
Soaps, shampoos?
Are you really taking
all this stuff?
Why not?
It's-it's built into the price
of the room.
Yeah, but you don't need...
What is this?
Thread.
Score.
Where are
the disposable cameras?
What disposable cameras?
The cameras.
Remember last night
I asked you to take them.
No, you didn't.
Yes. Remember?
Right before we cut the cake
I went up to you and I said...
Oh, yeah.
You came up to me
and asked me
if I could do you a favor
and then my Uncle Murray
came up to you
and handed you a check
and then you said,
"Why do they call it a check?
Why not a Yugoslavian?"
( laughs )
Yeah, then you did that.
So, you don't have
the cameras?
No. Sorry, man.
So what? What? They're gone?
Monica's going to freak.
Well, I'm sure
they're still somewhere
here in the hotel.
I'll help you look for them.
Great.
Yeah, in-in three minutes.
Hey.
Are you going to open
the presents without Chandler?
No.
It's just, you know, that...
Well, they're calling out to me.
I mean, this little guy
even crawled up in my lap.
Oh, come on, Chandler
wouldn't mind
if I open just
one present.
What do you think it is?
A little mirror
that when you look into it
you see yourself
as an old woman.
A tiny salt shaker!
Oh!
My God, for tiny salt.
Oh, wow. Okay.
Well, that was fun.
Oh, yeah.
That was fun.
Okay, I'm just going
to wait for Chandler
to open up the rest of them.
Okay.
Whew!
Although, you know
this is part of a...
salt and pepper set.
I guess, you know, it may just
count as half a present.
What do you think?
Well, I guess it's okay
to open one more
if it's part of a set.
You know,
it's probably this one.
Or this one.
Hi.
MONICA:
Hey, how are
you feeling?
Do you have any
morning sickness?
Shh! The guys don't know yet
do they?
No.
Joey and Ross don't know
anything
and Chandler still thinks
that Phoebe's pregnant.
Oh.
PHOEBE:
That's right.
Chandler does still think
I'm pregnant.
He hasn't asked me
how I'm feeling
or offered to carry my bags.
Oh, I feel bad for the woman
who ends up with him.
After you, of course.
RACHEL:
Well, don't worry.
I promise that you will
only have to be pregnant
for a few more hours
'cause I'm going
to tell the father today.
Ooh, is it someone
in this building?
Is it that tall guy
from the first floor?
Ooh, no!
What? I think he's cute.
Well, then, you have his baby.
Believe me, I'm trying.
Well, you know, it is so weird.
I mean, you're going
to tell this guy today
and he has no idea
what's going to happen.
No.
PHOEBE:
Yeah.
Yeah, you're just going
to knock on his door
and change his life forever.
You're like Ed McMahon
except without the big check...
or the raw sexual magnetism.
Yeah, well, I guess
it is pretty big news.
Pretty big? It's huge.
God, this guy doesn't have
a clue.
He's just walking down
the street thinking
"I had sex with Rachel Green.
I rock."
Then, bam!
He's a father,
everything's different.
Well, it's only different
if he wants it to be.
I mean, I'm not going
to ask him for anything.
Okay, then, he still has
this huge decision to make.
Now he's walking around
thinking
"Do I want to be a dad?"
And then, bam!
What was that bam?
I don't know.
He-he's hit by a bus
or something.
Hey.
RACHEL:
Hi.
Hey, Joey, what would you do
if someone that you slept with
told you that she was pregnant?
Who called here?
Did she sound blonde?
Huh? Did she have a accent?
I got to make a call.
I should never walked
into that sun glass hut.
RACHEL:
Joey... Joey
It's not you.
You didn't get anybody pregnant.
Oh.
Why would you scare me
like that?
What the hell's going on?
Is somebody pregnant?
Oh, yeah, that's me.
Oh, my God, Pheebs!
You're going to have a baby?
Yes, yes, I am.
Oh, my God
I'm going to have a baby!
Wait a minute.
Who's the father?
You don't know him.
It's not important.
He wants nothing to
do with me or the baby.
Well, who is this guy, huh?
Who is he?
'Cause I will track him down
and kick his ass.
David Lynn.
( door closes )
Who's David Lynn?
Oh, some guy from my gym.
A little annoying.
Chandler?
Hey, did you find the cameras?
No. Did you?
Yes.
That's why I'm under the table--
celebrating.
Well, I checked in
the lost and found.
I talked to
the manager.
No one's turned them in.
Well, this is great.
Those cameras were
the only thing
that was going
to cheer Monica up today.
She's really depressed.
Now, you guys
just got married.
Why is she
so depressed?
All my energy is going
into not asking that question.
I can't believe
I screwed this up.
I'm sorry, man.
Here's a thought.
This is the
same ballroom.
There's a band.
There's going to be plenty
of dressed-up people.
Are you suggesting
we dance our troubles away?
No, no, no.
I'm saying we-we buy more
of these at the gift shop
throw our tuxes back on
and take a few pictures.
All we have to do is make sure
not to get anybody else's faces.
Are you serious?
I'm just thinking
about your new bride
at home, okay?
Do you really want
to start your life together
by letting her down?
Marriage advice?
Really?
I'm telling you, this looks
exactly like your wedding.
Aren't these the same flowers?
I don't know. Monica
picked out the flowers.
Well, what about the chairs?
She picked those out, too.
How about the place settings?
That was her.
What did you do?
I was in charge
of the cameras.
Gift shop?
Hmm.
Hey.
Ooh, did you do it yet?
Not yet.
Oh.
Well, then
what are you doing here?
Are you about to do it?
Is it Gunther?
No.
Phoebe, it's not Gunther.
Thank God,
'cause that hair on a baby...
Phoebe, the father
is not here, okay?
I haven't told him yet
and I don't think
I can tell him at all now.
Why not?
Well, I don't know.
Let me think.
I was walking down the street,
thinking
"I'm going to tell the father
today," and then, bam!
Bus?
No, you.
Phoebe, you freaked me out.
You kept saying
how huge this all is.
Well, but it is huge.
I know
but I was just thinking
about how huge it was for me.
I didn't even go
to how huge this is going to be
for the father.
You're thinking about this
way too much.
Just tell him
and get it over with.
It's like ripping off
this Band-Aid.
Quick and painless. Watch.
Ow, mother of...
See?
Ooh. Are we opening presents?
No, no.
I shouldn't
have even opened these.
Joey, I am out of control!
Joey, you have to do me a favor.
No matter what I say,
no matter what I do
please do not let me open
another present, okay?
Okay.
Give me one more.
Hey.
Oh, good--
you're here.
Uh, Pheebs, listen, uh
sit down.
I got something
I want to say.
All right.
Um...
it's a scary
world out there--
especially for a single mom.
Now, I've always felt
that you and I have
a special bond, so...
Phoebe Buffay,
will you marry me?
Oh, my God.
Joey...
Oh, yeah, I'll marry you.
You can't marry him.
Hey, lady, your day's over.
It's my turn.
Phoebe...
What? Why can't she marry me?
I can and I will.
She's not pregnant.
It's Rachel.
Rachel's the one who's pregnant,
okay?
Oh, my God.
Hey!
I think he would notice
when you didn't have a baby
in nine months.
It's Joey.
( no audio )
I can't believe it.
Rachel's pregnant?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Well, who's the father?
We don't know.
Oh... I wonder if
it's that dude?
There's a dude?
Who? Who is it?
About a month ago, this guy
spent the night with Rachel.
Now, I didn't see who it was,
but...
Was that story over?
The guy left this.
( gasping )
Oh, my God.
I know who the father is.
People have got to
finish their stories.
Uh, excuse me.
Could you take a picture
of us, please?
Oh, of course.
Uh, would you take one
of us?
Uh, yeah. Sure.
Click.
It didn't click.
I heard it.
See?
But there was no flash.
Why won't you
take our picture?
Oh, yeah, I'll-I'll take,
I'll take your picture.
Um, your finger
was covering the lens.
Who are you, Ansel Adams?!
Get out of here!
Look, I feel really bad
about how
I freaked you out before
so, I called the father
and asked him
to meet you here
so you could tell him. Go.
Wha... hey, wait a minute.
Phoebe, how do you even know
who the father is?
I may play the fool at times,
but...
I'm a little more
than just a pretty blonde girl
with an ass that won't quit.
I believe this
belongs to the father
of your baby.
Oh, God.
Oh, he's in
there right now?
Uh-huh.
Now, you can turn around
or you can go in there
and rip the Band-Aid off.
What do you want to do?
Uh...
Let's rip.
Really? Are you sure?
Oh, Phoebe.
Okay, sorry. Yeah.
Hey, Rach.
Why don't you
go up on stage?
I'll get a picture of
you doing the speech.
Okay, okay.
( glasses tinkling )
Will the owner
of a 1995 Buick LeSabre
please see the front desk?
Your car is about to be towed.
That's my car.
A '95 LeSabre?
Yes.
A green LeSabre?
I'm sorry,
I meant a blue LeSabre.
Yes, green-blue.
Well, go.
Go move it!
Okay. Ready for
the last picture?
Yeah.
Get ready to run.
Congratulations
on your wedding.
So, what's this about?
Rachel has something
that she wants to tell you
and, um, I believe that
this is your red sweater?
No. This is my red sweater.
Oh, no.
Can I get anyone
a coffee, or...
poison? No? Just for me?
Okay.
What's going on,
Rach?
Nothing. Phoebe kind
of made a mistake.
But, you know, you do
wear that sweater a lot.
Are you involved in
some kind of dare?
You know, I'm actually glad
Phoebe called.
I know we broke up
'cause you thought
I wasn't mature enough
but I've really grown up
and I think
we should get back together.
Oh, it's just not
the right time.
It is the right time.
Okay.
I'm ready for more.
Tag...
Come on, Rach,
let's give it another try.
I'm having a baby.
Oh.
You can go.
Thank you.
I don't know how any
of these got opened!
You opened them all?
I know, I know!
I am a terrible person.
Chandler's never going
to trust me
with anything ever again.
Oh, hey,
you got my parents' gift.
Yeah, what is that?
I think it does something
to salami.
Hey
how did it go?
Yeah, what did Tag say?
Tag is not the father.
And Joey knows now?
I do, Rach, I do,
and I am so happy for you.
( chuckles )
Oh, wow, you didn't even try
to unhook my bra.
So, are you ever going
to tell whoever it is?
Yeah, I will.
I'm just not up for it tonight.
Hey, Rach, listen,
no matter what this guy says
I want you to know you're
not going to be alone in this.
I'm not?
No.
Listen, I, uh...
It's a scary world out there,
especially for a single mom.
Aw... Joey...
Uh, I've always felt
like you and I have
this special bond, you know?
So, Rachel Green,
will you marry me?
What?
What?!
Pheebs,
give me the ring back.
No!
Joey, oh, you're so sweet.
You are so, so sweet, honey.
But I'm not looking
for a husband.
I understand.
Now, if you will excuse me
I'm going to go
and lie down.
I can't say that didn't hurt.
But I'll take you back,
Joey Tribbiani.
Uh, yeah, Pheebs,
listen, about that.
Ooh, a Salami Buddy!
There you go.
We're back.
Great! We're hanging
in the kitchen.
Let's stay
It's picture time.
Now, you are going
to love these.
Here's a picture of Ross...
and that's me...
and that's me and Ross.
Oh, and here's
a picture of
our first kiss
as a married couple.
Wow, that is
a great picture.
Huh?
Yeah.
And interesting
because I found the cameras
in one of our bags.
Huh. Didn't see that coming.
Okay, so, this
isn't a picture
of our first kiss
but it is a picture
of my first kiss
with, with this lady.
( clearing throat )
Which, by the
look on your face
I'm sure you'll remember
so we don't need...
there's no need...
if we can just...
How about I take
the real pictures
and get them
developed right now?
That would be a good idea.
Okay.
You opened all the
presents without me?
I thought we were supposed
to do that together.
You kissed another woman?
Call it even?
Okay.
Well, I'm going to go get these
in some water.
You stole those
from these people's wedding?
No, I took them
from the hotel lobby.
They think they can charge me
for some dirty movie
and a bag of Meshuga Nuts,
they got another thing coming.
Hey, my sweater.
I've been looking for this
for, like, a month.
Oh, my God!
Hey. How you doing?
Good. Good.
Long time no see.
Yeah.
I like your sweater.
Oh, hey, right
back at you.
( both chuckling )
It's crazy about Rachel, huh?
Yeah. Well, she's
one crazy lady.
So, whose is it?
Um, I, I don't know,
some Italian guy.
Come on, read
your own label.
See you later.
Okay.
( sotto voce ):
He is so weird.